http://thorntonplastics.com/privacy-policy

Loading... Please wait...
Menu
Compare (0 Item)
SqueezeTops
Snap Cap Vials: 100 ct.
Snap Caps (Lids)
Natural Plastic Jars
Jars: 100 ct.
SqueezeTops
Snap Cap Vials: 100 ct.
Snap Caps (Lids)
Natural Plastic Jars
Jars: 100 ct.
PRIVACY POLICY
Thornton Plastics recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of our customer's personal and financial information. Thornton Plastics believes that protecting your valuable personal and financial information is one of our most significant responsibilities. Therefore, Thornton Plastics has instituted strict policies regarding your privacy. Thornton Plastics does not sell or rent our customer's names, addresses, email addresses or other personal information. When you register with Thornton Plastics you give us your consent to treat your personal data in accordance with this online privacy policy and for the purposes described below.
What Thornton Plastics Collects
Thornton Plastics collects information our customers give us, in order to provide our customers with the service they deserve. We study our customers' and visitors' use of our websites so we can improve our services and enhance your Thornton Plastics experience. When you register with Thornton Plastics, you give us your name and email address. Thornton Plastics does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen. If you are under thirteen, please ask your parents to register or exit this website.
How Thornton Plastics Uses Information You Provide
When you visit this website or send E-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically, therefore you: (1) consent to receive communications from us electronically, including communications by email or by notices posted on our website; and (2) agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirements that such communications be in writing.
Does Thornton Plastics Share Your Information With Other Entities?
Thornton Plastics does not sell or rent our customer's names, addresses, email addresses or other personal information. In order to maintain our website and enhance our customer communications, Thornton Plastics contracts with selected third parties. As necessary, your personal information may be shared with these third parties, solely for the purpose of assisting Thornton Plastics in these endeavors and subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations. We do not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, unless required by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding. If Thornton Plastics is acquired by another entity, information about Thornton Plastics customers may be part of the transfer.
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Quick Links
Contact Us
About Us
Shipping and Returns
Privacy Policy
Copyright 2020 Thornton Plastics. All Rights Reserved. | Sitemap |
All prices are in USD.
